<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Collected Writings on Home</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Collected Writings on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Team Sports</title>
      <link>/posts/team-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/team-sports/</guid>
      <description>The lads all used to have a grand time playing 5 a side before Covid came along, but can they get back into the swing of things?
Click here to read in PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death by Data</title>
      <link>/posts/death-by-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/death-by-data/</guid>
      <description>Leanne, Trye and Charlotte are struggling to progress during their flat&amp;rsquo;s board game night, until Trey pulls his phone out and inadvertently invites in an unwanted guest&amp;hellip;
Click here to read in PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Indomitable Human Spirit</title>
      <link>/posts/the-indomitable-human-spirit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-indomitable-human-spirit/</guid>
      <description>The Indomitable Human Spirit is a 3000 word story focusing on the human response to unending disaster
Click here to read in PDF or continue below
“Papa! What news?”
Peter spoke as he looked up from spooning soup into the waiting mouth of Gramps, turning in his seat to catch the haunted eyes of his father, slouched in their hovel’s doorway.
“The armies, they’ve finally met. Down at Bosun’s Creek.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Company Culture</title>
      <link>/posts/company-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/company-culture/</guid>
      <description>Conmpany Culture is a short, 3 people play that can be staged with just three chairs and a table (beyond this the limit is your imagination).
The play&amp;rsquo;s subject matter focuses on the farce of modern coproate environments.
Click here to read in PDF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milquetoast Romance</title>
      <link>/posts/milquetoast-romance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/milquetoast-romance/</guid>
      <description>Jill and Ryan formerly orbited similar social circles, but haven’t seen each other since those heady, pre-Covid days. Their chance meeting in a coffee shop may mark the start of a whirlwind romance, or perhaps something a little more grounded&amp;hellip;
Click here to read in PDF</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
